Guide to the Harper Theater Dance Festival Records, 1961-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
Harper Theater Dance Festival records 1961-1984
American Dance Festival Archives
Harper Theater Dance Festival.
11.3 linear feet
The Harper Theater Dance Festival Records (1965-1979) presented Chicago audiences with more than a decade of annual performance seasons from a variety of celebrated dance companies. Originating in 1965 as the brainchild of Bruce and Judith Sagan, proprietors of a series of local, neighborhood newspapers in Chicago, the Festival also served as an important milestone in American modern dance as the pilot program for the National Endowment for the Arts Residency Touring program. Favorite performers included Merce Cunningham, Alwin Nikolais, Paul Taylor, José Limón, and Murray Louis. The collection includes financial records, production requirements, clippings, correspondence, posters, programs, tickets, photos, negatives, 35 mm slides, video and audio reels, and several small objects.
ADF.010
Language: Material in eng
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Patrons must sign the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The Harper Theater Dance Festival Records were received by the American Dance Festival Archives as a gift in 1999.
Historical Note
The Harper Theater Dance Festival (1965-1979) presented Chicago audiences with more than a decade of annual performance seasons from a variety of celebrated dance companies. Originating in 1965 as the brainchild of Bruce and Judith Sagan, proprietors of a series of local, neighborhood newspapers in Chicago, the Festival also served as an important milestone in American modern dance as the pilot program for the National Endowment for the Arts Residency Touring program. Favorite performers included Merce Cunningham, Alwin Nikolais, Paul Taylor, José Limón, and Murray Louis.
Contemporary ballet companies, such as the Boston Ballet, Robert Joffrey's City Center Ballet, and the fledgling Pennsylvania Ballet Company, also found a place in the Festival in the early years (1965-1966). In later years, Judith Sagan, then sole producer of the Festival, brought newcomers such as Louis Falco, Bella Lewitzky, Wendy Perron, James Cunningham, Donald McKayle, Pilobolus Dance Theatre, and Viola Farber to Chicago (1970-1979). In an effort to diversify Festival offerings (and reach out to new donors), Mrs. Sagan also started the Chicago Dance Film Festival in 1974. Unfortunately, audiences in Chicago never reached the level necessary to continue funding the Festival and it was eventually abandoned in 1979.
Chronology of Performers
1965 Alba-Reyes Spanish Dance Company Paul Taylor Robert Joffrey Ballet Company Edward Villella and Patricia McBride Nala Najan Merce Cunningham Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater
1966 Murray Louis Boston Ballet Company Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus Daniel Nagrin Paul Taylor Glen Tetley Pennsylvania Ballet Company
1967-1968 Paul Taylor Alwin Nikolais Merce Cunningham Glen Tetley Paul Taylor José Limón Erick Hawkins
1969 Anna Sokolow Alwin Nikolais Merce Cunningham
1970 José Limón Alwin Nikolais Paul Taylor
1970-1971 Murray Louis Merce Cunningham Paul Taylor Alwin Nikolais
1972-1973 Acme Dance Company Inner City Dance Repertory Company Viola Farber Louis Falco
1973-1974 Bella Lewitzky Manuel Alum Pilobolus Dance Theatre Perron and Jarosolow Murray Louis Ze'eva Cohen
1975 Merce Cunningham
1979 Pilobolus Dance Theatre Alwin Nikolais Laura Dean Bella Lewitzky Paul Taylor 5 by 2 Plus
Collection Overview
The collection contains the institutional records of the Harper Theater Dance Festival, public relations and publicity materials of dance companies, as well as the personal files of the collection's donor, Judith Sagan. The materials housed within the collection are in a variety of formats, including paper-based records, photographs, 35 mm slides, programs, newspaper clippings, large-format posters and publicity materials, audio reels, open reel video, and several objects.
The bulk of the materials were collected or created during the running of the Festival (1965-1979), with additional records (e.g. souvenir programs, professional membership records, financial records, etc.) collected by the donor following the Festival's demise.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged into four series: Institutional Records, Company Files, Personal Files, and Photography.
Subject Headings
Cunningham, Merce; Limón, José.; Louis, Murray; Nikolais, Alwin; Sagan, Bruce; Sagan, Judith; Taylor, Paul, 1930-; Modern dance; Modern dance -- United States -- History; Chicago (Ill.)
Detailed Description of Collection
- Institutional Records, 1961-1984, undated, (4 Boxes)
  The Institutional Records series of the Harper Festival Dance Collection is arranged alphabetically by organizational function and date. Records are specific to the Festival and include advertising proofs and ads, professional correspondence, invoices, bank statements, checks, bulk mailing contents, IRS documentation, grant applications, newspaper reviews of performances, press kits (for companies performing and for entire Festival), contracts with companies and vendors, technical production records, programs and tickets, school programming records, and notes. Original item labels on the audio and video reel boxes are transcribed here, even though spelling is particular to original usage and creator agency (e.g. WorkPring collection).
  - Advertising, undated (Box 1)
    Printer's Plates
  - Advertising, undated (Box 1)
    Photocopied newspaper advertisements
  - Advertising, undated (Box 1)
    Newspaper advertisements
  - Advertising, 1965-1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1965-1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1966 (Box 1)
    Print proofs
  - Advertising, 1966 (Box 1)
    Print ad placements in Chimera and brochure
  - Advertising, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1969 (Box 1)
    Photocopied newspaper advertisements and radio spot script
  - Advertising, 1970 (Box 1)
    Radio station advertising guide
  - Advertising, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1970 (Box 1)
    Radio spot script draft and final copy
  - Advertising, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    Print proofs, photocopied newspaper advertisements, drafts of ads
  - Advertising, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    Newspaper advertisements and radio spot script
  - Advertising, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
    Manuscript draft fundraising letter
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
    Mixed professional correspondence
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Finance, undated (Box 1)
    Mixed financial documentation
  - Finance, undated (Box 1)
  - Finance, undated (Box 1)
  - Finance, undated (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    Box Office ticketing reports
  - Finance, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970-1978 (Box 1)
    Federal Tax Returns
  - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    Invoices
  - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    Bank statements
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
    Box Office
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1972 (Box 1)
    Check stubs
  - Finance, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Finance, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Finance, 1979-1984 (Box 2)
  - Finance: Chicago Dance Foundation, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Finance: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Finance: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Finance: Harper Dance Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
    Tax Exemption
  - Fundraising: Local, undated (Box 2)
    Mixed development records
  - Fundraising: Local, undated (Box 2)
    Donation mailers
  - Fundraising: Local, 1970, undated (Box 2)
  - Fundraising: Local, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
  - Fundraising: Local, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Fundraising: Local, 1978 (Box 2)
    Local donor mailing list
  - Fundraising: Local, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Fundraising: Strategy, undated (Box 2)
    Brochures from donor organizations
  - Grants: Ford Foundation, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
    Mixed paper records for grant application
  - Grants: Ford Foundation, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Ford Foundation, 1971 (Box 2)
    Financial documentation
  - Grants: Ford Foundation, 1971-1972, undated (Box 2)
    Mixed grant documentation records
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, undated (Box 2)
    Nikolais company dossier
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1967-1968, undated (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1968 (Box 2)
    Modern Dance Festival in Illinois report
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1968-1974 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council, 1979 (Box 2)
    Member mailing list
  - Grants: The National Corporate Fund for Dance, 1973 (Box 2)
    Grant marketing brochure
  - Grants: Illinois Arts Council/NEA, 1972 (Box 2)
    Dance company residency reports for grant recipients
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 2)
    Company residency availability
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
    Coordinated Residency Touring Program records
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1969 (Box 2)
    Choreography Commission records
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1973 (Box 2)
    NEA grant process guidelines
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1973 (Box 2)
    Artists in Schools records
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1975 (Box 2)
    Dance Touring Program brochure
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1976 (Box 2)
    Grant guidelines
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1977 (Box 2)
    Challenge Grants brochure
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1977 (Box 2)
    NEA newsletter
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Legal, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    Illinois Arts Council contract
  - Legal, 1968 (Box 2)
    City of Chicago Festival permission certificate
  - Legal, 1970 (Box 2)
    Mixed contracts
  - Legal, 1970-1977 (Box 2)
    IRS audit records
  - Legal, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
    Venue company contracts
  - Legal, 1972 (Box 2)
    Illinois Arts Council company contracts
  - Legal, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Legal, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Legal, 1974 (Box 2)
    Venue contract
  - Legal, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
    Company contracts release forms
  - Legal, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Legal, 1978 (Box 2)
    Release form
  - Legal, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    Company contracts
  - Legal, 1979 (Box 2)
    Theater Lease contract
  - Legal, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Legal: Chicago Dance Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
    Harper Dance Foundation formation documentation
  - Legal: Harper Dance Foundation, undated (Box 2)
    Harper Dance Foundation mission statement
  - Legal: Harper Dance Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    Foundation dissolution documentation
  - Notes, undated (Box 2)
    Handwritten notes, internal memos
  - Notes, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1965 (Box 2)
    Spiral bound notebook
  - Notes, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1973 (Box 2)
    Internal memo
  - Notes, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Notes, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Press, undated (Box 2)
    Photocopied newspaper articles and performance reviews
  - Press, undated (Box 2)
    Newspaper articles and performance reviews
  - Press, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Press, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Press, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Press, 1965 (Box 10)
    Oversized newspaper review (Joffrey, R.)
  - Press, 1965 (Box 9)
    Photocopied newspaper articles
  - Press: Harper Dance Festival, 1965-1979 (Box 9)
    Newspaper advertisements articles and performance reviews
  - Press, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Press, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Press, 1966 (Box 10)
    Oversized newspaper review (Tetley, G.)
  - Press, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Press, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Production, undated (Box 3)
    Technical production records
  - Production, undated (Box 3)
    Mixed production records
  - Production, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Production: Lighting Plots, 1969, 1972 (Box 9)
    Alwin Nikolais 1969 performance lighting plot; Inner City Dance Repertory Company 1972 performance lighting plot
  - Production, 1971 (Box 3)
    Wall calendar with handwritten notes
  - Production, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
    Itinerary
  - Production, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1974 (Box 3)
    Venue production report
  - Production, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Production, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Production: Taylor, Paul, 1979 (Box 10)
    Lighting plot
  - Production: Harper Theater Blueprint, undated (Box 10)
    Blueprint
  - Production: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Production: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 3)
    Dance Films booklet by John Mueller
  - Production: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 3)
    Vendor film listings and Dance magazine (April 1969)
  - Production: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 3)
    Dance films directory
  - Program Copy, undated (Box 3)
    Biographies and program drafts
  - Program Copy, undated (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, undated (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, undated (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Program Copy, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 3)
    Festival performance programs
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 3)
    Mixed public relations records
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 3)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 3)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 3)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1966 (Box 4)
    Full press kit
  - Public Relations, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1970 (Box 4)
    Mailer copy
  - Public Relations, 1970 (Box 4)
    Flyers and mailers
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1979 (Box 4)
    Logo proofs
  - Public Relations, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations, 1979, undated (Box 4)
  - Murray Louis with Studs Terkel at WFMT 1/6/71(1 of 2) (Box 8)
    Audio reel
  - Murray Louis with Studs Terkel at WFMT 1/6/71 (2 of 2) (Box 8)
  - Merce Cunningham and John Cage with Studs Terkel at WFMT 1/1971 (1 of 2) (Box 8)
  - Merce Cunningham and John Cage with Studs Terkel at WFMT 1/1971 (2 of 2) (Box 8)
  - Cunningham, Merce: Posters, 1975 (Box 9)
    Harper Theater Dance Festival posters
  - Louis, Murray: Publicity (Box 9)
    Harper Theater Dance Festival publicity materials
  - Posters and Publicity: 1972-1973, undated (Box 9)
  - Posters: Dance Film Festival (Box 9)
    Dance Film Festival publicity
  - Sokolow / Tetley / Cunningham (M.): Publicity, undated (Box 10)
    Clippings collage posters (3)
  - Hawkins / Taylor / Limón: Publicity, undated (Box 10)
    Clippings collage posters (8)
  - Cunningham, Merce: Posters and Publicity, 1975 (Box 10)
    Merce Cunningham Harper Theater Dance Festival residency poster
  - Posters and Publicity, 1965 (Box 10)
    Poster
  - Posters and Publicity, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Posters and Publicity, 1971 (Box 10)
    Posters (2)
  - Cunningham, Merce: Posters and Publicity, undated (Box 10)
  - Posters and Publicity, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
    Posters (4)
  - Louis, Murray: Posters and Publicity, undated (Box 10)
  - Public Relations: Film Festival, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Public Relations: Harper Dance Foundation Board, 1979 (Box 4)
  - School Programming, undated (Box 4)
    Reviews, school directories, lecture notes
  - School Programming, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
    Mixed programming records
  - School Programming, 1968 (Box 4)
    Lecture notes for Merce Cunningham
  - School Programming, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    Sign-up lists
  - School Programming, 1969 (Box 4)
  - School Programming, 1970 (Box 4)
  - School Programming, 1970 (Box 4)
  - School Programming, 1971 (Box 4)
    Attendance records
  - Alum Close-Up WorkPring Collages Take 1 (Box 8)
    1/2 inch open reel video
  - Alum Dance 1) Deadliner I and II Color (Box 8)
  - Allum: Collage / Jaroslow and Perron / 1x2x4 (Box 8)
  - Jaroslow and Perron No.3 (Box 8)
  - Jaroslow and Perron Workshop No.1 (Box 8)
  - Pilobolus No.1 (Box 8)
  - Alum: Tiviom 1) Collage 2) E to Nijinsky (Box 8)
  - Alum: Close-up 1) Collage 2) E to Nijinsky (Box 8)
  - (Untitled) (Box 8)
  - JandP Master Class No.2 (Box 8)
  - Pilobolus No.3 (Box 8)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre (Box 8)
  - Pilobolus (Box 8)
  - Tickets: Student Coupons, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    Student ticket coupons
  - Tickets: Student Coupons, 1970-1973 (Box 4)
  - Tickets, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    Ticket reservation forms
  - Tickets, 1969 (Box 4)
    Tickets
  - Tickets, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Tickets, 1968-1973 (Box 4)
  - Tickets, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Tickets, 1975-1979 (Box 4)
  - Tickets: Dance Film Festival, 1974 (Box 4)
- Company Files, 1964-1992, undated, (2 Boxes)
  The Company Files series is composed of publicity and marketing materials, posters, and newspaper clippings of dance companies and/or performers. It is divided into two sub-series: Festival Performers and Non-Festival Performers.
  - Festival Performers, 1962-1979, undated
    The Festival Performers sub-series is arranged alphabetically by performer. Records include posters, programs, articles, and reviews of non-Festival performances, as well as general press kits.
    - Ailey, Alvin (Box 5)
      Mixed public relations records, programs
    - Ailey, Alvin: Press (Box 5)
      Newspaper articles and non-Harper Theater Dance Festival performance reviews
    - Ailey, Alvin: Press (Box 5)
      Photocopied newspaper articles and non-Harper Theater Dance Festival performance reviews
    - Alba-Reyes (Box 5)
    - Alba-Reyes: Press (Box 5)
    - Alba-Reyes: Press (Box 5)
    - Alum, Maunel (Box 5)
    - Alum, Maunel: Press (Box 5)
    - Boston Ballet Company (Box 5)
    - Boston Ballet Company: Press (Box 5)
    - Boston Ballet Company: Press (Box 5)
    - Cage, John (Box 5)
    - Cage, John: Press (Box 5)
    - Cohen, Ze'eva (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, James (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, James: Press (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Merce (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Merce (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Merce (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Merce: Press (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Merce: Press (Box 5)
    - Press Clippings: Merce Cunningham, 1964-1982 (Box 9)
    - Cunningham, Merce: Posters and Publicity, undated (Box 10)
      Clippings collage posters (2)
    - Dean, Laura (Box 5)
    - Dean, Laura (Box 5)
    - Falco, Louis (Box 5)
    - Falco, Louis: Press (Box 5)
    - Falco, Louis: Posters, undated (Box 10)
      Non-Harper Theater Dance Festival posters
    - Farber, Viola (Box 5)
    - Farber, Viola: Press (Box 5)
    - 5 by 2 / 5 by 2 Plus (Box 5)
    - 5 by 2 / 5 by 2 Plus: Press (Box 5)
    - Goslar, Lotte (Box 5)
    - Goslar, Lotte: Press (Box 5)
    - Goslar, Lotte: Posters, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Hawkins, Erick (Box 5)
    - Hawkins, Erick: Press (Box 5)
    - Hawkins, Erick: Press (Box 5)
    - Inner City Dance Repertory Company (Box 5)
    - Inner City Dance Repertory Company: Press (Box 5)
    - Inner City Dance Repertory Company: Press (Box 5)
    - Jaroslow and Perron (Box 5)
    - Jaroslow and Perron: Press (Box 5)
    - Joffrey, Robert (Box 5)
    - Joffrey, Robert: Press (Box 5)
    - Joffrey, Robert: Press (Box 5)